UNITE HERE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6200/005 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE Local 23-25 Memorabilia
2004-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE
6200/005 MB
3.67 cubic feet
3.7 linear ft.
Memorabilia, awards.
7127377
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Clothing workers-- Labor unions--New York (State); Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); UNITE HERE (Organization); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); UNITE HERE (Organization)
7127377
- May Chin - In Honor of Your 22 Yrs of Service to the Community, the Labor Movement (plaque) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Better Chinatown Society, proudly salutes Unite Here Local 23-25. (plaque) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Presented to Mrs. May Chen - In Recognition of your outstanding contribution to the Flatbush Haitian Center, May 19, 2005 (plaque) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Achievement Award - May Ying Chen, NY Cosmopolitan Lions (plaque) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Artwork (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Framed artwork (figure in a Japanese costume) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- New York Immigration Coalition Builders of the New New York Award presented to May Chen, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Greater Blouse, Skirt & Undergarment Association (award), 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Labor Council of Latin American Advancement, New York City, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Hubei Federation of Trade Unions (Box 2, Folder 4)
- UNITE HERE! (painter's cap) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Save the Garment Center (button) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Community Excellence Award, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fabric swatches (Box 2, Folder 8)
- UNITE HERE! Shopping bag (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Projects from a class of students, (note included) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Spoon (gold with flower painted on it) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Paper fan - characters (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cassette tape (Chinese or Japanese characters on it) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Shoes (Box 2, Folder 14)
- UNITE HERE pin (Box 2, Folder 15)
- UNITE HERE! For Obama (stickers) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  3
- Brown and White cotton dress (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Beige and Black slacks (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brown belt (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Beige belt (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Black and White plaid cotton dress (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Green cotton jacket (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Red, Blue and White cotton, pleated skirt (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jacket, White, with green, red and blue polka dots (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Navy blue cotton jacket (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Black and white skirt (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Black and White top (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Red skirt (Box 4, Folder 5)